Tufts Hilltopper UP058
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Hilltopper
1946 -- 1971
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office for Campus Life
UP058
9 Volumes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issue of The Summer News and Hilltopper. They contained news and articles about summer programs at Tufts. The Tufts Summer News, a student newspaper, was created in July 1946 and existed until August 1948, when for its fourth volume it was retitled the Tufts Hilltopper. The Tufts Hilltopper continued production until 1971.
Biographical / Historical
Responsibility for new student orientation once fell under the pervue of the Orientation Committee. Currently, the Office for Campus Life takes a leadership role in the planning and implementation of New Student Orientation.
- Tufts Hilltopper, 1946 -- 1971; UP058.001; 9 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of The Tufts Summer News. It was created in July 1946, and existed until August 1948, when, for its fourth volume, it was retitled the Tufts Hilltopper. The Tufts Hilltopper continued production until 1971.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - The Tufts Summer News, Thursday July 11, 1946; UP058.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Thursday July 18, 1946; UP058.001.001.00002 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Thursday July 25, 1946; UP058.001.001.00003 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Thursday August 1, 1946; UP058.001.001.00004 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Thursday August 8, 1946; UP058.001.001.00005 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Thursday August 16, 1946; UP058.001.001.00006 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Wednesday July 9, 1947; UP058.001.002.00001 (Box Volume 2)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Wednesday July 16, 1947; UP058.001.002.00002 (Box Volume 2)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Wednesday July 23, 1947; UP058.001.002.00003 (Box Volume 2)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Wednesday July 30, 1947; UP058.001.002.00004 (Box Volume 2)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Wednesday August 6, 1947; UP058.001.002.00005 (Box Volume 2)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Wednesday August 13, 1947; UP058.001.002.00006 (Box Volume 2)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Wednesday July 14, 1948; UP058.001.003.00001 (Box Volume 3)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Wednesday July 21, 1948; UP058.001.003.00002 (Box Volume 3)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Wednesday July 28, 1948; UP058.001.003.00003 (Box Volume 3)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Wednesday August 4, 1948; UP058.001.003.00004 (Box Volume 3)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Wednesday August 11, 1948; UP058.001.003.00005 (Box Volume 3)
  - The Tufts Summer News, Wednesday August 18, 1948; UP058.001.003.00006 (Box Volume 3)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Friday July 8, 1949; UP058.001.004.00001 (Box Volume 4)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 13, 1949; UP058.001.004.00002 (Box Volume 4)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 20, 1949; UP058.001.004.00003 (Box Volume 4)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 27, 1949; UP058.001.004.00004 (Box Volume 4)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday August 3, 1949; UP058.001.004.00005 (Box Volume 4)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday August 10, 1949; UP058.001.004.00006 (Box Volume 4)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 12, 1950; UP058.001.005.00001 (Box Volume 5)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 19, 1950; UP058.001.005.00002 (Box Volume 5)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 26, 1950; UP058.001.005.00003 (Box Volume 5)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday August 2, 1950; UP058.001.005.00004 (Box Volume 5)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday August 9, 1950; UP058.001.005.00005 (Box Volume 5)
  - Hilltopper Extra, August 16, 1950; UP058.001.005.00006 (Box Volume 5)
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Monday July 2, 1951; UP058.001.006.00001 (Box Volume 6)
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 11, 1951; UP058.001.006.00002 (Box Volume 6)
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 18, 1951; UP058.001.006.00003 (Box Volume 6)
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 25, 1951; UP058.001.006.00004 (Box Volume 6)
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday August 1, 1951; UP058.001.006.00005 (Box Volume 6)
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday August 8, 1951; UP058.001.006.00006 (Box Volume 6)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room.
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Tuesday July 1, 1952; UP058.001.007.00001 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 9, 1952; UP058.001.007.00002 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 16, 1952; UP058.001.007.00003 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 23, 1952; UP058.001.007.00004 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 30, 1952; UP058.001.007.00005 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday August 6, 1952; UP058.001.007.00006 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Monday June 29, 1953; UP058.001.007.00007 (Box Volume 7)
    Volume, issue
    VIII, 1
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Tuesday July 7, 1953; UP058.001.007.00008 (Box Volume 7)
    VIII, 2
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Tuesday July 14, 1953; UP058.001.007.00009 (Box Volume 7)
    VIII, 3
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Tuesday July 21, 1953; UP058.001.007.00010 (Box Volume 7)
    VIII, 4
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Tuesday July 28, 1953; UP058.001.007.00011 (Box Volume 7)
    VIII, 5
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Tuesday August 4, 1953; UP058.001.007.00012 (Box Volume 7)
    VIII, 6
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Monday June 28, 1954; UP058.001.007.00013 (Box Volume 7)
    IX, 1
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 7, 1954; UP058.001.007.00014 (Box Volume 7)
    IV, 2
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 14, 1954; UP058.001.007.00015 (Box Volume 7)
    IX, 3
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 21, 1954; UP058.001.007.00016 (Box Volume 7)
    IX, 4
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 28, 1954; UP058.001.007.00017 (Box Volume 7)
    IX, 5
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday August 4, 1954; UP058.001.007.00018 (Box Volume 7)
    IX, 6
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 5, 1955; UP058.001.007.00019 (Box Volume 7)
    Volume
    XII
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 13, 1955; UP058.001.007.00020 (Box Volume 7)
    XII, 2
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 20, 1955; UP058.001.007.00021 (Box Volume 7)
    [alumni] Tufts ranks 28 in populaiton reference bureau survey; Painting of murals by artists Matthew W. Boyhan and Nathaniel J. Jacobson [includes photo]; Academic Honors; pp. 1,8. [Administration] Bi-weekly payment plan explained. p. 1. Alpha Kappa Delta.
    XII, 3
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 27, 1955; UP058.001.007.00022 (Box Volume 7)
    XII, 4
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday August 3, 1955; UP058.001.007.00023 (Box Volume 7)
    XII, 5
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday August 9, 1955; UP058.001.007.00024 (Box Volume 7)
    XII, 6
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 2, 1956; UP058.001.007.00025 (Box Volume 7)
    XIII, 1
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 11, 1956; UP058.001.007.00026 (Box Volume 7)
    XIII, 2
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 18, 1956; UP058.001.007.00027 (Box Volume 7)
    XIII, 3
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 25, 1956; UP058.001.007.00028 (Box Volume 7)
    XIII, 4
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday August 1, 1956; UP058.001.007.00029 (Box Volume 7)
    XIII, 5
  - The Tufts Hilltopper, Tuesday August 7, 1956; UP058.001.007.00030 (Box Volume 7)
    XIII, 6
  - Tufts Hilltopper Monday, July 7, 1957; UP058.001.008.00001 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Tuesday, July 16, 1957; UP058.001.008.00002 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Tuesday, July 23, 1957; UP058.001.008.00003 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Tuesday, July 30, 1957; UP058.001.008.00004 (Box Volume 8)
    Alumni night at Arena theater
  - Tufts Hilltopper Tuesday, August 6, 1957; UP058.001.008.00005 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Tuesday, June 30, 1958; UP058.001.008.00006 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 9, 1958; UP058.001.008.00007 (Box Volume 8)
    [Abbott, Donald G.] "College Views New Role in Sputnik Age" p. 1, 4.
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 16, 1958; UP058.001.008.00008 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 23, 1958; UP058.001.008.00009 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 31, 1958; UP058.001.008.00010 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday August 6, 1958; UP058.001.008.00011 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Monday, June 29, 1959; UP058.001.008.00012 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 8, 1959; UP058.001.008.00013 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 13, 1960; UP058.001.008.00014 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 22, 1959; UP058.001.008.00015 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 29, 1959; UP058.001.008.00016 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday June 27, 1960; UP058.001.008.00017 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 6, 1960; UP058.001.008.00018 (Box Volume 8)
    [Administration, 1960] Tufts' two vice-presidents on WNAC [Northeastern University radio station].
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 13, 1960; UP058.001.008.00019 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 20, 1960; UP058.001.008.00020 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 29, 1960; UP058.001.008.00021 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 5, 1961; UP058.001.008.00022 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 12, 1961; UP058.001.008.00023 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 19, 1961; UP058.001.008.00024 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 26, 1961; UP058.001.008.00025 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, August 2, 1961; UP058.001.008.00026 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, August 9, 1961; UP058.001.008.00027 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, June 25, 1962; UP058.001.008.00028 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 5, 1962; UP058.001.008.00029 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 11, 1962; UP058.001.008.00030 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 18, 1962; UP058.001.008.00031 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 25, 1962; UP058.001.008.00032 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, August 1, 1962; UP058.001.008.00033 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Monday, July 1, 1963; UP058.001.008.00034 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 10, 1963; UP058.001.008.00035 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 17, 1963; UP058.001.008.00036 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 24, 1963; UP058.001.008.00037 (Box Volume 8)
    Catherine L. Allen [Faculty] Elected president of Ammerican Association of Health, Physical Education and Recreation (incl. photo).
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 31, 1963; UP058.001.008.00038 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 7, 1963; UP058.001.008.00039 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, August 7, 1963; UP058.001.010; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_4540cef99428d573a4a964d3e7f0caaf, Box 10)
    Volume, Number
    XX, 6
  - Tufts Hilltopper Monday, June 29, 1964; UP058.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Monday, July 8, 1964; UP058.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Monday, July 15, 1964; UP058.001.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Monday, July 22, 1964; UP058.001.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Monday, July 29, 1964; UP058.001.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Monday, August 5, 1964; UP058.001.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Monday, June 28, 1965; UP058.001.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Wednesday, July 7, 1965; UP058.001.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Wednesday, July 14, 1965; UP058.001.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Wednesday, July 21, 1965; UP058.001.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Wednesday, July 28, 1965; UP058.001.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Wednesday August 4, 1965; UP058.001.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Wednesday Monday June 27, 1966; UP058.001.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Wednesday Monday July 6, 1966; UP058.001.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Wednesday Monday July 13, 1966; UP058.001.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Wednesday Monday July 20, 1966; UP058.001.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Wednesday Monday July 27, 1966; UP058.001.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Wednesday August 3, 1966; UP058.001.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Monday June 26, 1967; UP058.001.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesnday July 5, 1967; UP058.001.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 12, 1967; UP058.001.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 19, 1967; UP058.001.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 26, 1967; UP058.001.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper Wednesday August 2, 1967; UP058.001.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Monday July 1, 1968; UP058.001.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 10, 1968; UP058.001.009.00026 (Box 9)
    [Admissions] More stringent. pp. 1, 2.
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 17, 1968; UP058.001.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 24, 1968; UP058.001.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 31, 1968; UP058.001.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, August 7, 1968; UP058.001.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Monday, June 30, 1969; UP058.001.009.00031 (Box 9)
    [Admissions] Admissions policies.
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 16, 1969; UP058.001.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 23, 1969; UP058.001.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, July 30, 1969; UP058.001.009.00034 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday, August 6, 1969; UP058.001.009.00035 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Monday, June 29, 1970; UP058.001.009.00036 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 8, 1970; UP058.001.009.00037 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 15, 1970; UP058.001.009.00038 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 22, 1970; UP058.001.009.00039 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 29, 1970; UP058.001.009.00040 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday June 28, 1971; UP058.001.009.00041 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 7, 1971; UP058.001.009.00042 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 14, 1971; UP058.001.009.00043 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 21, 1971; UP058.001.009.00044 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday July 28, 1971; UP058.001.009.00045 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Hilltopper, Wednesday August 5, 1970; UP058.001.009.00046 (Box 9)